Main Menu:
1.New Game
2. Load Game
3. Setup
4. Quit

Russian Translation:

1. Новая Игра
2. Загрузить Игру
3. Настройки
4. Выход


Setup Menu:
Ur-Quan Masters Setup
1. Graphic Options
2. PC/3DO Compatibility Options
3. Sound Options
4. Resources Options
5. Configure Controls
6. Advanced Options
7. Quit Setup Menu


Introduction:
    It is the year 2165. 

    Four years ago you traveled the galaxy, assembling the scattered forces of the old Alliance of Free Stars, striving to free the human race from Ur-Quan enslavement. 

    You succeeded. 

    The Ur-Quan fled, leaving their Hierarchy forces in disarray. The Chmmr have emerged as the new leaders of known space and have asserted their authority. 

    Slave worlds have been freed. And a new era of peace has emerged. 

    For their service to the Ur-Quan defense, Hierarchy battle thralls have been punished. 

    The New Alliance of Free Stars is rebuilding decimated homeworlds, and continues to drive out the scattered Ur-Quan from known space. 

    After many years of travelling the galaxy fighting the Ur-Quan, a peaceful life on Unzervalt with Talana beckons. You have devoted your years to the study of Precursor technology, not willing to be involved in diplomacy, politics or military operations. 

    But your new life must wait. 

    Alliance command at Procyon has received a distress signal from a Shofixti scout deep in unknown space. The urgent, garbled message refers to an enormous machine that destroyed several scout vessels upon contact. Then... only static. 

    The Chmmr have asked YOU to lead an expedition to travel to the distress site far from Earth to track down the Shofixti and neutralize this artifact. 

    As you punch through the fabric of truespace, you wonder: Are you ready for this? 